mydoorsign.com 2017-08-31

# MyDoorSign.comDisclaimer

SmartSign knows that your privacy matters to you, and so we have established this privacy policy to let you know how we use your information. Our privacy policy is also subject to our Terms and Conditions.

### 1. Information we collect 

We do not collect personal information unless you voluntarily provide it to us. For example, we collect your name, email address, and your password when you register an account; when you order goods from us, we collect your billing address, shipping address, phone number and payment information. We also store your order history. You can choose to store your contact and billing information with us.

This site also uses cookies. Cookies are small data files stored on your computer, and most browsers are set up to accept cookies by default. Cookies do not track any personal information, but we may use them to identify you as a past customer, for instance. We use third-party cookies, like Google, for analytics, and those third-party cookies may be placed on your computer. [You can opt out of advertising cookies by clicking this link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). We do not respond to web browser “do not track” signals. We do not collect data on your online activities over time across third-party websites.

Our servers automatically log some information that comes from you, like which browser you are using, your IP address, what IP address you came to SmartSign from, and how you navigate within our site. This information cannot be used to identify you personally, but it helps us to determine if someone else is accessing your account without authorization.

We also track your usage history, such as your search history and which content you have accessed. This history lets you easily backtrack to a location you’ve previously visited.

If you receive emails from us, we use web beacon technology to track whether you have clicked on individual email advertisements.

### 2. How we use your information

We may use your personal information to personalize your profile, maintain SmartSign, make improvements to the site, and to communicate with you. We will share your personal information with third parties only under the following conditions:

  * To provide products or services you have requested. Among other things, this includes order confirmations, invoices, and customer service communications. 
  * For marketing purposes, like to send you catalogues or marketing emails.
  * When disclosure is required by law, like if we receive a court order telling us to turn over data. We do not give your data to law enforcement unless they present us with a court order.
  * To investigate suspected fraud, illegal activities, threats to any person, or violations of our Terms and Conditions.
  * When we hire contractors to perform services for us. This includes companies that do payment processing, order fulfilment, catalogue printing and marketing for us. For instance, if you check out through PayPal or Amazon, we submit your personal information to them.
  * If you donate to any of SmartSign’s charity partners at checkout, SmartSign will give that charity partner your contact information if you choose to receive SmartSign emails.
  * If SmartSign is purchased by or merged with another company. We will provide you with reasonable notice if that happens by updating this page.

### 3. Control of your information

If you do not want to us to share your personal information with our partners, receive catalogues, or marketing emails, you can unsubscribe at the My Account page. Even if you do opt out, we may still use your personal information to communicate with you regarding your account, fulfil your orders, or if required by law.

To deactivate your account, please email [customerservice@smartsign.com](mailto:customerservice@smartsign.com) or call us at 800-952-1457. 

### 4. Security

The personal information you provide us, including your payment information, is stored on access-controlled, secure servers, and the people who work on SmartSign data are all required to keep your information confidential and secure. All data you submit to SmartSign is encrypted and stored in PCI-compliant data centers. In the event a security breach happens, we will promptly inform you.

### 5. Privacy of minors

We do not collect information from anyone that we know is a minor under 18. If we become aware that you are a minor under 18, your account is subject to cancellation and your data is subject to deletion.

### 6. Deleted data

When you cancel your account, your data will be deleted automatically within 30 days.

### 7. Changes & Questions

We will notify you if we change this policy by listing it on your account or by posting changes on this page. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, email us at [customerservice@smartsign.com](mailto:customerservice@smartsign.com).

_This privacy policy was last updated on October 20, 2016._
